

Alvan Fathurahman

Mobile Developer

https://www.linkedin.com/in/alvan-fathurahman-7767a121a/https://alvanfathurahman.netlify.app/ +62-859-4765-0520 fathuralvan28@gmail.com

Summary

I am a graduate of Software Engineering from SMK Wikrama Bogor. Currently, I work and study at Swadharma Institute of Business Technology. With 1 year of experience as a fullstack developer and another year in mobile front end development, I am actively building my career in these fields.

HARD SKILLS

- Flutter
- PHP
- Laravel
- HTML CSS
- Bootstrap
- React Js
- Git
- Ajax
- Javascript
- Jquery
- · Google Cloud Big Query
- MYSQL
- Rest API & Consume API

SOFT SKILLS

- Can work as individual or team
- Adaptable
- Great attitude
- Easy to learn new things

LANGUAGES

- Indonesian
- English

WORK EXPERIENCE



Full Stack Web Developer
JINNO (Jakarta Innovation)-Part time
January June 2022 - October 2023

- Made a website with Laravel, Bootstrap, Javascript, Ajax, API.
- Find a bug at the code and fix it.
- Cooperate with other developers.
- Using the GitLab platform to develop code.
- Implement google cloud big query



Frontend Mobile Developer
Pt. Maju Aman Sejahtera - Full time
June 2023 - Now

- Made a mobile apps using Flutter
- Flutter Bloc architecture
- Integration use Dio
- Using the GitLab platform to develop code.
- MVVM Clean architecture

FORMAL EDUCATION



Wikrama Bogor Vocational Highschool

Major: Software Engineering Year of Graduation: 2023



Institut Teknologi dan Bisnis Swadharma Major: Information Systems Department

2023 - Now

INFORMAL EDUCATION



Alterra Academy

Type: Free Bootcamp for mobile development 2022